(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ビターチョコデコレーション
作詞・作曲：syudou
Bitter Choco Decoration
Lyrics/Composition: syudou
人混みに馴染まないように
So as not to blend in with the crowd
愛されないように
So as not to be loved
期待しないように
So as not to have expectations
かと言って角が立たないように
But also so as not to cause any friction
気取らぬように
So as not to be pretentious
目立たぬように
So as not to stand out
誰一人傷つけぬように
So as not to hurt a single person
虐めぬように
So as not to bully
殺さぬように
So as not to kill
かと言って正体がバレないように
But also so as not to let my true nature be exposed
威張らぬように
So as not to be arrogant
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れるように
So as to forget even light jokes and lip service
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
So as to always smile and scatter charm around
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
とにかく言わずもがな召し上がれ
Anyway, it goes without saying, please help yourself
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
不和と嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
Discord and dislikes must be properly fixed
頭空っぽその後に
After the head is empty
残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains is the real thing
きっと君だって同じこと
Surely, you are the same
さあところで一つ伺いますが
Now, by the way, I have one question
全ては...
Everything is...
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
無駄に期待をさせぬように
So as not to give useless hope
離れさせぬように
So as not to let them leave
願わせぬように
So as not to let them wish
でも殺気は閉じ込めぬように
But so as not to trap the bloodlust
笑わすように
To make them laugh
笑わせるように
To be made to laugh
人ちゃんと敬うように
To properly respect others
崇めるように
To revere
讃えるように
To praise
でも嫌味にならないように
But so as not to be offensive
ふざけないように
So as not to mess around
集団参加の終身雇用 へらへら行っちゃって
Lifelong employment in a group, went along grinning
あれ 前髪超絶最強じゃん とか どうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Oh, your bangs are totally the best, saying things like that even though I don't care
マイバイブルも限界集落的 社会の終末です
My bible is a marginal village-like social apocalypse
決して発狂しないように
So as never to go insane
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes lonely love pollutes you
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
立つ鳥の跡 濁さぬあとの
A departing bird leaves no trace...
はじめはあんなに奔放な
At first, being so uninhibited
大言壮語 並べたが
Lined up big talk
嫌々々々 嘘つきの味
No, no, no, no, the taste of a liar
いんやはや しかし今日が初めてで
Geez, but today is the first time
こんな事まで 君センスあるよ
Even something like this, you have sense
嗚呼 F.U.C.K.Y.O.U. ビターチョコデコレーション
Ah, F.U.C.K.Y.O.U. Bitter Choco Decoration
厳守せよ 礼儀作法
Observe etiquette strictly
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Longing for the ideal everyone wants
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
個性や情を全部焼き払い
Burn away all individuality and emotion
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Kill greed and ego and bury them in the dirt
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
僕は大人にやっと成ったよ ママ
I've finally become an adult, Mama
明日の規則のその先を
Beyond tomorrow's rules
地獄は続く どこまでも
Hell continues everywhere
ああ だからどうか今だけは
Ah, so please, just for now
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
Keep the feelings of your childhood
不様（ぶざま）に晒してやってこうぜ
Let's show our unseemly sides
ああ 思い出したわ あの時の生真面目さを
Ah, I remembered the seriousness of that time
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
サイコロ...
A dice...
5が出た。
I rolled a five.
ん？何これ？
Hmm? What is this?
椅子？
A chair?
One, two, one...
Deal with the devil
Up and down 浮世の常
Up and down, it's just the way of the world
組んだ端から 解（ほど）けない
Once it's built, it won't unravel
感じたいの そのまま
I want to feel it as it is
出し抜いて 騒げ
Outsmart them and make some noise
行き着く先には
At the destination
Hell or hell?
この世界に残る たったひとつの勝者こそが正義
The only winner remaining in this world is justice
女は度胸 地を這わせるの あいつを
A woman needs nerve; I'll make that guy crawl on the ground
やれること 何だってやる 私は賭ケグルイのクイーン
I'll do whatever it takes, I'm the Kakegurui Queen
お見通しよ じゃんけん
I see through you, Rock-Paper-Scissors
読みきって 全勝だ
I'll read it all and win every time
Dealを待って 見透かして 私のモノにする
Wait for the deal, see through it, and make it mine
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair
Only one, I'll take it over
Able to win, you want it more
Yeah, 満たせやしないわ
Yeah, it won't satisfy me
Dealを待って Go up and down たまらないわ スリル
Wait for the deal, go up and down, this thrill is irresistible
誰にも触らせない このマネー
I won't let anyone touch this money
Only one, I'll take it over. Sa, come on 覚悟決めて
Only one, I'll take it over. Now come on, make up your mind
トドメ刺してあげる My hand
I'll give you the finishing blow, my hand
欲しがりね 良いじゃない 待て Baby
You're greedy, aren't you? That's fine. Wait, baby
タイマン 負けない 感じさせてよ LOVE Me
Man-to-man, I won't lose, make me feel LOVE Me
あなたの正体は ほら...
Your true identity is, look...
頂いてあげる
I'll take it from you.
秘密って甘い毒
Secrets are a sweet poison.
仕掛けて 罠にハメるわ
I'll set it up and trap you.
奪い誘うような指
Fingers that beckon and snatch away...
舌を這わせたら最後
Once I let my tongue crawl, it's the end.
何も知らないような顔で
With a face like you know nothing...
躍らすわ あなたを
I'll make you dance.
It's Deal with the Devil
読み切ってレッツショウダウン
Read it all, and let's showdown.
目を疑う変幻自在の
Ever-changing, making you doubt your eyes.
どんな小さなぜるだって
No matter how small the cheat is...
私の目をごまかせないわ
You can't fool my eyes.
I am the gambler, aite wa... gomen maade
I am the gambler, forgive me regardless of who it is.
屈服させてあげる
I'll make you yield.
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my prey escape.
唇を濡らして いただきます
Wetting my lips... Bon appétit.
Oh, my babe!
ダイヤのジャックで手が揃わ
With the Jack of Diamonds, the hand is complete.
笑みはこれ始末だわ
This smile is the end of the line.
鮮やかなポーカーフェイス
A brilliant poker face.
一分の隙も見せやしないわ
I won't show a single opening.
人生感じてんの
I'm feeling life.
お遊びは終わりまで
The play is until the very end.
見てばかりいないで
Don't just watch.
私が欲しいから
Because I want you.
負けるのは怖い？
Are you afraid of losing?
読み切ってレッツショウダウン
Read it all, and let's showdown.
目を疑う変幻自在に
To an ever-changing state that defies the eyes.
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair...
I am the gambler, aite wa... furuete iru no yo
I am the gambler, the opponent is trembling.
どこまでも行くわ
I'll go as far as I can.
目を疑う変幻自在の
Ever-changing, making you doubt your eyes.
誰にも触らせない このままで
I won't let anyone touch it like this.
I am the gambler, sa come on kakugo kime te
I am the gambler, so come on, make up your mind.
灰になるまで撃って
Shoot until it turns to ash.
惜しがる気持ちはまだ、baby?
Still feeling reluctant, baby?
誰にも負けない感じさせて
Make me feel like I won't lose to anyone.
ロミオ
Romeo.
おっと。あれ？椅子なくなっちゃった。
Oops. Huh? The chair is gone.
はぁー。もう少し座らせてほしかったー。
Phew. I wanted to sit a little longer.
はい、みんな！見えてる？聞こえてる？
Hey, everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒し系ハーフエルフ、
アキロゼこと、アキ・ローゼンタールです！
I'm the healing half-elf of Hololive,
Aki Rosenthal, also known as Akirose!
アロハ、アロハ、アロハ、アロナ〜！
Aloha, aloha, aloha, Alona~!
はぁー、えー、今回のアキロゼ生誕祭2026へようこそ！
Phew... welcome to Akirose Birthday Festival 2026!
早速ね、なんか色々行われていたんですが、一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか、ぜひ最後まで必見、お見逃しなくお願いします！
A lot of things have been happening right from the start, but please stay tuned until the very end to see how this live show unfolds!
今回のライブのハッシュタグは、「#アキロゼ生誕祭2026」、こちらをつけてXにたくさんポストしてね！
The hashtag for today's live is '#AkirozeSeitansai2026', so please use it and post a lot on X!
もちろん、可愛いスクショ、えー、もたくさん撮って、合わせて投稿してください！
Of course, take lots of cute screenshots and post them too!
ライブが終わった後、アキロゼ見に行きまーす！見てねー！
Akirose will go check them out after the live! Stay tuned!
あ、チャンネル登録もよろしくね！
Oh, and please subscribe to the channel!
オッケー？たくさん撮って？はい、ありがとう！
Okay? Did you take lots? Yes, thank you!
お？お？なんだ？なに、なに、なに？うーん？
Oh? Oh? What's this? What, what, what? Hmm?
ていうか、ここどこなんだろう？うーん、あ？
By the way, where am I? Hmm, oh?
おおー、あんなとこにルーレットがある。え、回るのかな？
Whoa, there's a roulette wheel over there. Huh, I wonder if it spins?
お！え！回った！えー、すごーい！回ったー、えー！見事！
Oh! Whoa! It spun! Whoa, amazing! It spun! Wow! Splendid!
どうなるんだろう...
What's going to happen...?
あ、え、あ、え？
Ah, eh, ah, eh?
なに？なに？
What? What?
どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen?
ピース？
Peace?
んん？なんだ？
Hmm? What is it?
Ah happy
悩める人よ
O troubled soul
Ah lucky
となれば儲けもの
If so, it's a bargain
Ah happy
今更目覚めよ
Wake up now
いい子でいるんだしね
You're being a good child
目を逸らした過去も
The past you looked away from
退屈な未来も
The boring future
感性に従え
Follow your intuition
やれやれ
Good grief
Ah happy
Ah lucky
Be happy
UNDEAD
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
ねぇねぇねぇ なんだかどうして
Hey, hey, hey, why is it
戦ってるような気がするの
That I feel like I'm fighting?
止められない 止めたくもない
Can't stop, don't want to stop
今の自分
The current me
ノックノック死んでる
Knock, knock, I'm dead
透明な無礼で大正解
A transparent rudeness, perfectly correct
痛い痛い 痛い記憶の奥
Ouch, ouch, deep within painful memories
残念 もういないのに
Too bad, I'm not here anymore
あれ そっちがアイロニー
Wait, you're the one that's irony
ねえ 透かされてるのは 今の自分
Hey, the one being seen through is the current me
ナンセンス 消えないヘイト
Nonsense, the hate won't fade
癒えようがコンプレックス
Though it heals, the complex remains
取り憑かれてるみたい
I feel like I'm possessed
巻き付いたまま
Still entwined
まだ離れない
Still won't let go
在りし日の自分
My former self
UNDEAD
信じられない お前とマイノリティ
Unbelievable, you and the minority
生きてることが問われ続ける形
The form where being alive is constantly questioned
絶頂に甘んじて満足するなよ
Don't settle for the peak and be satisfied
幸せになろうとしないなんてひょーだ
Not trying to be happy is just a farce
この世この世は奇怪奇怪ファンタジー
This world, this world is a strange, strange fantasy
次は鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
Will an ogre or a snake appear next?
出会って会ってやっと始まる物語
Meeting and meeting, finally the story begins
敵かお化けかはのかその巨大ピースピース
Whether it's an enemy or a ghost, a giant peace peace
Ah, the future can change the past
Past the future
Love for the future
ねえねえねえ なんだかどうして
Hey, hey, hey, why is it
未来に安堵がのうのうと
That the future feels so nonchalant?
今もまだ
Even now
体に機能
Functioning in my body
ような気がして
I feel as if
もう随分生きてる
I've already lived for a long time
時間だテンプレート食傷
Time for the template, satiety
肯定なんて聞きごとの気配もない
No sign of any affirmation to hear
残念 詰んだ経験
Too bad, stuck experience
因果経済 正しさは退屈の進化
Causal economy, correctness is the evolution of boredom
今日は刺激を頂戴
Give me some stimulation today
飽きちゃった？
Are you bored?
投げ出した？
Did you give up?
ナンセンス 獲って代わるガイダンス
Nonsense, the guidance taking over
セルフコンプライアンス
Self-compliance
透かされてくみたい
I feel like I'm being seen through
吸い尽くして
Drain it all
あれもこれもどれも同じ味がする
This, that, and the other all taste the same
UNDEAD
信じられない お前とマイノリティ
Unbelievable, you and the minority
いつのような過去も未来も今にあるんだ
Any past or future exists in the now
生きてることを愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill the fact of being alive with sincerity
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending
UNDEAD
信じられない お前と居てるんだし
Unbelievable, since I'm here with you
幸せを諦めてしまうな 人であれ
Don't give up on happiness, be human
ただ苦しみに慣れて耐えているだけじゃ
Just getting used to and enduring pain is
死んでるも同然 しかばねのアンデッド
No different from being dead, a corpse-like undead
Ah happy
悩める人よ
O troubled soul
Ah lucky
となれば儲けもの
If so, it's a bargain
Ah happy
目覚めよ 生きていんだろう
Wake up, you're alive aren't you?
不幸に浸るも幸せになるのも
Whether indulging in misery or becoming happy
もう全部全部お前だ
It's all up to you
古今東西
All times and places
ピースピース
Peace peace
Ah, the future can change the past
Past the future
Love for the future
人となるところ 逸れ行くところ
Where one becomes human, where one stray away
このお化けものばかりものかてピースピース
Whether it's all just ghosts or something, peace peace
愛♡スクリーム！
作詞：aim
作曲：DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
Ai ♡ Scream!
Lyrics: aim
Composition: DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
おしえてもっとあなたのこと
Tell me more about yourself
Help me more more more Help me more more more
きかせてもっとあなたのこえ
Let me hear more of your voice
Let me your more more Let me your more more
こんなドキドキ抑えきれない
I can't suppress this heartbeat
Oh I need you Oh I need you
友達はそつぎょう 運命の私
Graduating from being friends, the fated me
みつけてほしいな
I want you to find me
勇気を出して
Have some courage
見つめる作戦
Operation: Staring
緊張がいっぱい　Wow
I'm so nervous, wow
止まれない　Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋　この愛で
I can't stop, yeah yeah yeah
With this love, with this affection
ねむねむに溶けちゃうよ
Yeah Yeah Yeah　気づいてマイダーリン
I'm melting into sleepiness
Yeah yeah yeah, notice me, my darling
とどけて大好き
I'll send you my love
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
マルちゃん！
Maru-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミントよりも　あなた！
Rather than chocolate mint, I like you!
プルルちゃん！
Pururu-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
シチリア産ベリーフレーバーよりも　あなた！
Rather than Sicilian berry flavor, I like you!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも　あなた！
Rather than cookies & cream, I like you!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き！　アイスクリーム！
Of course we love it! Ice cream!
止まれない　Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋　この愛で
I can't stop, yeah yeah yeah
With this love, with this affection
ねむねむに溶けちゃうよ
Yeah Yeah Yeah　気づいてマイダーリン
I'm melting into sleepiness
Yeah yeah yeah, notice me, my darling
ちょうだい大好き
Give me your love
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
お願い見つけてマイダーリン
Please find me, my darling
お願い気づいてマイダーリン
Please notice me, my darling
勇気を出して
Have some courage
近づく作戦
Operation: Getting closer
鼓動が触れて　Wow
Our heartbeats touch, wow
止まれない　Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋　この愛で
I can't stop, yeah yeah yeah
With this love, with this affection
ねむねむに溶けちゃうよ
Yeah Yeah Yeah　気づいてマイダーリン
I'm melting into sleepiness
Yeah yeah yeah, notice me, my darling
それはあなた
That's you
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・アイスクリーム！
スクリーム！　叫びましょう！
I-I-Ice cream!
Scream! Let's shout it out!
スクリーム！　アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
おー、元気もらって、面白くって、オレンジで、
Oh, someone energetic, funny, orange-themed,
シャンパンコール得意な人いないかな？
And good at champagne calls... anyone?
それ俺じゃないかー！
Isn't that me?!
ちょっとでいいから見せてくれないか？
Can you show me just a little?
お前のセクシー・フェロモンで俺メロメロ
I'm head over heels for your sexy pheromones
潰れちゃいそうでもイケナイの？
Is it bad even if I feel like I'm going to burst?
非常に高鳴る鼓動　止められないわ
My heart is pounding so hard, I can't stop it
交わす言葉の記憶遠く
The memory of our exchanged words is distant
口もと　動きに揺れ動く
Swaying with the movement of your lips
濡れた髪をなでた
Stroked your wet hair
そして　あーああああ
And then... ahhhh...
ABC　続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's just no good, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない?
'Cause deep down, it's different, isn't it?
オレの青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to end hotly deep inside
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's gotta be you or I won't like it
オレはイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
あー
Ah
赤い糸なんて嘘っぱち
The "red thread of fate" is just a lie
でも下心でさえ信じたいな
But even with ulterior motives, I want to believe
オレは正しい　君も正しい
I'm right, you're right
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed anymore
飛ばした端から胸うずかせた
The fleeting moments made my heart ache
お芝居よりも盛り上げるよ
I'll hype it up more than any play
息が耳に触れた二人ああー
Our breaths touched our ears, the two of us... ahhh...
ABC　続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's just no good, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない?
'Cause deep down, it's different, isn't it?
私の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to end hotly deep inside
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's gotta be you or I won't like it
私イケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
交わす言葉の記憶辿り
Tracing the memories of words exchanged
唇の動きにギュッと吸い込んだ
I inhaled deeply at the movement of your lips
濡れた髪をなでた
Stroked your wet hair
そして　あーああああ
And then... ahhhh...
あー
Ah
ABC
ABC　続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's just no good, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない?
'Cause deep down, it's different, isn't it?
俺たちの青春そんなもんじゃない
Our youth isn't just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to end hotly deep inside
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's gotta be you or I won't like it
俺はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
絡み合う糸は君と俺
The intertwined threads are you and I
俺を結ぶ赤い糸
The red thread that binds me
(吐息)
(Exhale)
おー、はぁ、うわー！
Oh, whew, wow!
はぁ、みんな、はぁ、来てくれて...ありがとう！
*Breathing hard* Everyone... thank you for coming... Thank you!
ということで、お友達が来てくれたので
So, since my friends have come,
せっかくなので自己紹介してもらおうと思います！
I'd like them to introduce themselves!
まずは、ぷるるちゃんから！
First up, Pururu-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
天使と悪魔のハーフ、ぷるぷるえんじぇるでびる、甘乙ぷるるです！
Half-angel and half-devil, the Puru Puru Angel Devil, Amaoto Pururu here!
悪魔じゃ！お誕生日おめでとう！
I'm a devil! Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、とっても楽しかったです！
Man, that was so much fun!
ありがとう、最高！
Thank you, that was the best!
そして、続いて、かるびちゃん！
And next, Karubi-chan!
はい、お肉の国のお姫様、赤見かるびです！
Yes, the princess of the Kingdom of Meat, Akami Karubi here!
アキローゼ、誕生日おめでとう！
Aki Rosenthal, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
3Dライブって、友達とのライブ初めてだからさ、
About 3D lives, this is my first time doing one with friends,
マジで嬉しかったよ！
so I'm seriously happy!
ありがと、呼んでくれて！
Thanks for inviting me!
またやろうぜ！
Let's do it again!
またやろう！
Let's!
素晴らしい！そして最後に、ずずさん！
Wonderful! And finally, Zuzu-san!
はい！僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで、自己紹介だけさせてください！
Yes! I'm sure there are some people who don't know me, so please let me introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー、症状自体は爺々、
It's raining pitter-patter, my condition is geezerly,
僕の名前は、ず、ず、ず、ず、ずずでございます！
my name is Zu-zu-zu-zu-Zuzu!
いや、お誕生日おめでとう！
Man, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
つかれたー！
I'm beat!
おやおや...
Well, well...
お忙しい人気者だ！
What a busy popular person!
お忙しいな！
So busy!
アキちゃんおめでとう！
Congratulations, Aki-chan!
後でめちゃくちゃ遊ぼう！
Let's play a ton later!
めちゃくちゃ遊ぼう！
Let's play a lot!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
はぁ〜、賑やかで楽しかった！
Phew, that was lively and fun!
JANE DOE
作詞・作曲：秋野空輝
Lyrics & Composition: Akino Sorateru
Hmm-hmm~
まるでこの世界で
It's like in this world,
二人だけみたいだね
we're the only two people.
なんて少しだけ
Just a little bit
夢を見てしまっただけ
of a dream I ended up seeing.
爪先に月明かり
Moonlight on tiptoes,
花束の香り
the scent of a bouquet,
弓に触れる指
fingers touching the bow.
さよならもう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I must go now,
何もかも忘れて
forget everything.
はぁ...
Sigh...
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on glass,
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちて行く
with every pain, blood flows and drops away.
お願いその赤い
Please, follow those
足跡を辿って
red footprints,
会いに来て
and come to see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish being released into a rusted pool,
屑箱の中 隠した林檎
an apple hidden in the trash can.
しなびた君の肌に抜ける傷跡
Scars fading on your withered skin,
犬のように泳いだ迷子
a lost child swimming like a dog.
どこに居るよ
Where are you?
何をしてるの
What are you doing?
この世を間違いで
Let's fill this world
満たそう
with mistakes.
側に居たよ
I was by your side,
遊びに行こうよ
let's go play.
どこに居るの
Where are you?
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on glass,
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちて行く
with every pain, blood flows and drops away.
お願いその赤い
Please, follow those
足跡を辿って
red footprints,
会いに来て
and come to see me.
まるで...
It's like...
...この世界で...
...in this world...
...二人だけ...
...we're the only two people...
...みたいだね
...isn't it?
Hmm-hmm~
なんて少しだけ
Just a little bit
夢を見てしまっただけ
of a dream I ended up seeing.
さ、選択の時だ。
Now, it's time to choose.
コイン。
Coin.
このコインは…
This coin is...
はは… そうか。君はそっちなんだね。
Haha... I see. You're on that side.
そっち？
That side?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
え…
Eh...
この後は君次第だよ。
After this, it's up to you.
Whisper Whisper Whisper
作詞・作曲：Azari
Lyrics & Composition: Azari
忘れられないのはこの目のせい
The reason I can't forget is because of these eyes
赤く残る過ち 甘噛みの跡
The red mistake remaining, the mark of a love bite
溢れ出す憂いは止め処もない
The overflowing sorrow is endless
誰もいない間に悪魔を唆す
Tempting the devil while no one is around
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The reason for the fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from deep within the walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔をあやかる
Escaping this cage and basking in the devil's favor
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where even the words I want to say are bitten back
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and spending time with the devil
I My Me 夢見ていたい あなたに
I My Me, I want to keep dreaming, for you
そっと気付かせてあげたいだけ
I just want to let you know softly
Oh あなたにも Oh あなたにも Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too, Oh, to you too, Oh, to you too
Keep My 傷を隠したい あなたに
Keep My, I want to hide my wounds, from you
そっと悩ませてあげたいだけ
I just want to make you worry softly
Oh あなたにも Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too, Oh, to you too
悪魔を唆す
Tempting the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The reason for the fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from deep within the walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔をあやかる
Escaping this cage and basking in the devil's favor
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where even the words I want to say are bitten back
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and spending time with the devil
BANG!!!
作詞：ryo (supercell) 作曲：Giga
Lyrics: ryo (supercell) Composition: Giga
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹っ飛べ BAN!!!
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blow it all away, BAN!!!
かかって来いマジョリティ 私に負けはなし
Come at me, majority, there's no losing for me
ここまでって引かれた そのボーダー誰のルール
That border drawn to say 'this far,' whose rule is it?
あの日乗り越えたウィークポイント
The weak point I overcame that day
強くなった私が笑い飛ばしてあげる
The stronger me will laugh it off for you
言いたいことは言う
I say what I want to say
やりたくないことはしない
I don't do what I don't want to do
悪意気にしない
I don't care about malice
みんな違うの当然だし 私も変わらない 目の前の自分
It's natural everyone is different, and I won't change, the self before me
(Every single day) I want to be free
Yes まだ終わりじゃないさ それじゃ何も変えられんな
Yes, it's not over yet, if so, nothing can be changed
(Every single day) I want it more
構わない自分勝手 生きてるんだって
I don't care about being selfish, because I'm alive
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) 生きてるんだって
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) Because I'm alive
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) ねえ生きてるんだって
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) Hey, because I'm alive
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) 歌えばいいのさ
(BAN!!! BAN!!!) It's fine to just sing
抗え 生まれたその時から選んできた地点
Resist, the point you've chosen since the moment you were born
思い出せ 私は私だ 不確かな事なんて
Remember, I am myself, uncertain things
何一つない 嘘じゃない 鳴り響け自分に
There's not a single one, it's not a lie, ring out to yourself
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹っ飛べ BAN!!!
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blow it all away, BAN!!!
振る舞うならさ このリリック回さ
If I'm going to act, I'll turn these lyrics
わからす 挑発 下向いて舌打ちからの はっ？
I'll make you understand, provocation, looking down, clicking my tongue, and then, 'huh?'
Excuse me?
言い返して頂戴
Tell me back
パンチライン　聞かせてあげる ah
I'll let you hear the punchline, ah
やってから考えな
Think about it after you do it
私が見つめてるから ah
Because I'm looking at you, ah
Everybody say I wanna be free
研ぎ澄ます　五感全部黙らす ah
Hone all five senses and shut them up, ah
目覚ませ起きろ
Wake up, get up
Wake up wake up
いっとけなら今だ
Go for it, it's now
ねえいっとけなら今だ
Hey, go for it, it's now
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since the moment I was born
思い出せ　私は私だ
Remember, I am who I am
不可能なことなど何ひとつもないさじゃないの
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since the moment I was born
思い出せ　あなたはあなただ
Remember, you are who you are
不可能なことなど何ひとつもないさじゃないの
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
なりたい自分に
To the person you want to be
好き嫌い　正しい I don't care フットペダル
Like, dislike, correct, I don't care, foot pedal
Bad Apple!!
流れてく時の中ででも　けだるさが
Even in the flowing time, listlessness
ほらグルグル回って　私から離れる
Look, it goes around and around, leaving me
心も見えないわ　そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I don't know
自分から動くこともなく　時の隙間に
Without moving on my own, in the gaps of time
流され続けて　知らないわ　周りのことなど
Kept being swept away, I don't know about my surroundings
私は私　それだけ
I am me, that's all
夢見てる　なにも見てない　語るも無駄な
I'm dreaming, seeing nothing, it's useless to talk
自分の言葉　悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
My own words, grieving only makes me tired
なにも感じず過ごせばいいの
I should just spend my time without feeling anything
戸惑う言葉　与えられても　自分の心
Even if given confusing words, my own heart
ただ上の空　もし私から　動くのならば
Is just absent-minded, if I were to move
すべて変えるのなら　黒にするわ
If I were to change everything, I'd make it black
こんな自分に　未来はあるの？　こんな世界に
Is there a future for a self like this? In such a world
私はいるの？　今切ないの？　今悲しいの？
Do I exist? Am I pained now? Am I sad now?
自分のことも　わからないまま
Without even knowing myself
歩むことさえ　疲れるだけよ　人のことなど
Even walking only makes me tired, as for others
知りもしないわ　こんな私も　変われるのなら
I don't even know them, if even I could change
もし変われるのなら　白になるわ
If I could change, I'd become white
流れてく時の中ででも　けだるさが
Even in the flowing time, listlessness
ほらグルグル回って　私から離れる
Look, it goes around and around, leaving me
心も見えないわ　そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I don't know
自分から動くこともなく　時の隙間に
Without moving on my own, in the gaps of time
流され続けて　知らないわ　周りのことなど
Kept being swept away, I don't know about my surroundings
私は私　それだけ
I am me, that's all
夢見てる　なにも見てない　語るも無駄な
I'm dreaming, seeing nothing, it's useless to talk
自分の言葉　悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
My own words, grieving only makes me tired
逃げよう
Let's run away
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
I should just spend my time feeling nothing
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if I'm given confusing words
自分の心
My heart is
ただ上の空
just somewhere else
もし私から動くのならば
If I were to move on my own
すべて変えるのなら黒にする
If I were to change everything, I'd make it black
動くのならば
If I move
すべて壊すわ
I'll break everything
悲しむならば
If you're sad
私の心白く変われる？
Can my heart change to white?
あなたのことも私のことも
Both you and me
すべてのこともまだ知らないの
I still don't know anything about it
重いまぶたを開けたのならば
If I open my heavy eyelids
すべて壊すのなら黒になれ
If I destroy everything, then let it turn to black
Yeah...
Magia
作詞・作曲：梶浦由記
Lyrics & Composition: Yuki Kajiura
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
The light of love that you will one day light in your eyes
時を越えて
transcending time
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
will surely break one of the dreams
壊すだろう
of a world rushing to its demise
ためらいを飲み干して
Drink up your hesitation
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
In the outcome of such greedy longings
はかない明日はあるの？
is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
I saw in my dreams as a child
闇さえ砕く力で
with a power that can even crush the darkness
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet you smiling
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands
手折られた花と勇気
are a plucked flower and courage
思いだけが頼るすべて
My feelings are all I have to rely on
光を呼び覚ます願い
a wish to awaken the light
いつか君も誰かのために強い力を
One day, you too will desire
望むのだろう
a strong power for someone else's sake
愛が胸を捕らえた夜に
On the night when love captured your heart
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
unknown words come to life
迷わずに行けるなら
If you can go without hesitation
心が砕けてもいいわ
it's okay if my heart shatters
いつも目前の悲しみに
To always face
立ち向かうための呪文が欲しい
the sorrow right before my eyes, I want a spell
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dreaming memory
私は眠らない明日
I am a sleepless tomorrow
二人が出会う奇跡を勝ち取るために
To win the miracle of the two of us meeting
進むわ
I will move forward
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands
手折られた花と刃
are a plucked flower and a blade
思いだけが生きるすべて
My feelings are all that keeps me alive
心に振りかざす願い
a wish to brandish in my heart
とらわれた太陽の輝く
The radiance of the captive sun
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
Back when I loved books about wonderland
願いはきっと叶うと教える
I believed in fairy tales
おとぎ話を信じた
that taught me wishes surely come true
光と影の中
Amidst light and shadow
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, the ancient magic
古の魔法を優しく
that was blooming in silence...
世界を変える力が
...whispers that the power
その手にあると囁く
to change the world is in those hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream
君と行く時の中で
within the time I spend with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
These feelings are all that live;
命を作るのは願い
what creates life is a wish.
うわあああー！イェーイ！
Waaaah! Yay!
アキちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！イェーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
いやー、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Man, thank you for coming today.
いえいえ、こちらこそですよ。呼んでくれてありがとう。
No, thank you as well. Thanks for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのにはちょっと理由があって。
Actually, there's a reason I invited you two.
お、なんだなんだ？
Oh? What's that?
前に、アキロゼの4周年の時に、
Previously, for AkiRose's 4th anniversary,
3人でKalafinaさんの曲歌わせてもらったんだけど。
the three of us sang a Kalafina song.
やりましたねー！めっちゃ良かったやつね！
We did! That was a really great one!
ハーモニーがね、そう。
The harmony, yeah.
もうね、ミオちゃんの歌も大好きだし、
I love Mio-chan's singing,
あずあずの歌も大好きだし、もうそのね、忘れられないの。
and I love Azu-azu's singing too. I just can't forget it.
忘れない。わかる、めっちゃわかる。
Won't forget. I know, I totally get it.
そう。だからもう一回、
Exactly. So I wanted to sing with the three of us
このライブステージで3人で歌いたくて、今日は来てもらいました。
on a live stage again, which is why I asked you to come.
嬉しい！ありがとうありがとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you, thank you!
そう、だからこれからね、これを機に、もっと3人で歌ったりとか、
So, taking this opportunity, I'd be so happy if we could
なんかそういうの挑戦できたらめっちゃ嬉しい。
try singing more together as a trio.
いいですね！ハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ。
Let's do it! Let's keep layering our harmonies.
え、いいの！？嬉しいー！
Really? Yay! I'm so happy!
なんかユニット名とか欲しいなー。
I want a unit name or something.
確かに、なんだろう。
True, what should it be?
え、なんかちょっと世界目指せるぐらいの。
Like, something where we can aim for the world.
世界！？
The world!?
世界の、世界のコンサートしようよ。
Let's do a world concert.
世界に驚く、我ら何かをね、したいということで。
Let's do something that will surprise the world.
この3人でライブとか、アコースティックとか、
With us three, like an acoustic live
オーケストラライブとか。
or an orchestral live...
うわー、良くないですか？そういうことをしてみたい。
Wow, wouldn't that be nice? I want to try that.
我らならできるかもしれない！おねがいします！
We might be able to do it! Please!
あれ？え？これは一体何ですか？
Huh? What's this?
もしかして、このライブでみんなからの、
Could it be, with the power from everyone
なんかいいパワーで。
at this live...
なんかいいパワー来てる！
Some good power is coming!
演出だ、それ。
That's visual effects.
なんだよ、そのパワー。
What is that power?
こちらがなんと、完成しました！
This has finally been completed!
実は、この後。
Actually, after this...
アキロゼの新曲が出ます！
AkiRose's new song will be released!
出たー！やったー！
It's out! Yay!
こちら、ま、今回のあのライブのま、テーマというか、
This song is themed after the grand theme
壮大なテーマがあるんですけど。
of this live performance.
そちらも詰まったような楽曲になっています。
It's a track packed with all that.
そしてライブ終わりの日付が変わる時に、
It will be released at midnight after the live,
リリースしますので、ぜひ買って聴いてください。
so please go listen to it.
イェーイ！みんな聴くぞー！
Yay! Everyone, let's listen!
ではでは、じゃあ次の曲に行きますか。
Now then, shall we move on to the next song?
次の曲。
Next song.
新曲お披露目。
Performing the new song.
なんだって！？
What!?
しちゃいます！
I'm going to do it!
今からってこと！？今から。
You mean right now!? Right now.
頑張ります！もう最後まで見逃せないですね。
I'll do my best! Don't miss it until the very end.
楽しみだー。アキちゃん頑張ってね！
I can't wait. Good luck, Aki-chan!
ありがとうー！またねー！
Thank you! See you later!
モノポリー
作詞・作曲・編曲：なるみや
Monopoly
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Narumiya
魅惑の言葉の
Captivating words
裏面に忍ばせた
Hidden on the reverse side
1mg(ミリグラム)のスパイス
A milligram of spice
たちまち華麗な
Instantly magnificent
指先で彩る
Colored with fingertips
本日のダイス
Today's dice
当たり前見てた景色じゃ
In the scenery I took for granted
生き残れないでしょう
You probably won't survive
率直に言って
To be frank
全てが欲しい
I want it all
一人勝ちオールイン
Winner-takes-all, All-in
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて
Trifling, and being trifled with
ゾクゾク
Thrillingly
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ
It's what you wanted, even if you get eaten, right?
最低だって滾るでしょ
Even if it's the worst, you're excited, right?
見透かして 見透かされて
Overlooking, and being overlooked
永遠に終わりはない
There's no end to eternity
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
Everything that's throbbing is non-fiction
嗜むはずでもたまには飲み過ぎて
Even if I only meant to enjoy a little, sometimes I drink too much
1回休み
Skip one turn
周りもざわつく思わぬうたた寝で
Everyone around me is buzzing from my unexpected nap
2回休み
Skip two turns
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ
Just with a sharp mind and intuition
手に入らないモノ
Some things can't be obtained
そこでいて見越されるならいい
It's fine if I'm being anticipated there
命懸けで楽しむわ
I'll enjoy it with my life on the line
天と地は案外近くない
Heaven and earth aren't as close as you'd think
この通り 命乞い
Just like this, begging for life
たかがモノポリー されど大勝負
It's just Monopoly, but it's a big match
決める思い 今宵は私が強い
Determined feelings, tonight I am strong
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて
Trifling, and being trifled with
ゾクゾク
Thrillingly
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ
It's what you wanted, even if you get eaten, right?
最低だって滾るでしょ
Even if it's the worst, you're excited, right?
見透かして 見透かされて
Overlooking, and being overlooked
永遠に終わりはない
There's no end to eternity
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
Everything that's throbbing is non-fiction
堕ちても昇ってもノンフィクション
Whether falling or rising, it's non-fiction
葛飾ラプソディー
作詞：森雪之丞 作曲：堂島孝平
Katsushika Rhapsody
Lyrics: Mori Yumino, Composition: Dojima Kohei
中川に浮かぶ
Floating in the Nakagawa River
夕日をめがけて
Aiming for the setting sun
小石を蹴ったら
If I kick a small stone
靴まで飛んで
Even my shoe flies away
ジョギングしていた
The person who was jogging,
大工の頭に
the carpenter foreman
ガキのままだと
He laughed and said
笑われたのさ
I'm still just a brat
どこかに元気を
Even if I dropped my energy
落としてきても
somewhere
葛飾亀有
Katsushika, Kameari
あくびをひとつ
I let out a yawn
変わらない街並みが
The unchanging townscape
妙に優しいよ
is strangely kind
中央広場で
At the central square
子供の手を引く
leading a child by the hand
ふと見たあの子は
that child I suddenly saw
懐かしい人
is someone I remember
ガムパッチンいけて
With a gum-snap prank
渡しそびれた
that I missed the chance to give
今も持ってるよと
'I still have it now', I said
からかわれたよ
and was teased
何にもいいこと
Even if nothing good
なかったけれど
ever happened
葛飾水元
Katsushika, Mizumoto
流れる雲と
With the floating clouds
ラプソディー口ずさみ
humming a rhapsody
少し歩こうか
shall we walk a little?
カラスが鳴くから
Since the crows are cawing
もう日が暮れるね
the sun is already setting
焼鳥ほおばり
Stuffing our cheeks with yakitori
ビール飲もうか
shall we drink beer?
トンボ釣り落とした
Many treasures from dragonfly fishing
数多の宝
dropped away
水元公園へと
Over Mizumoto Park,
夕日が落ちる
the setting sun goes down
明日もこうして終わるんだね
Tomorrow will end like this too, won't it?
隠し事はまた幸せだって
Secrets are a form of happiness too.
隠して気がついた
I realized by hiding it...
馬鹿な本音だったから
...because it was a foolish true feeling.
どこかに未練を落としても
Even if I leave some regret somewhere,
隠しきれないあくびをひとつ
I let out a single yawn I couldn't hide.
変わらない街並みが
The unchanging cityscape is...
妙に優しいよ
...strangely kind.
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆様、いかがでしたでしょうか？
Everyone watching AkiRoze Birthday Celebration 2026,
how did you enjoy it?
さて、ここからは大事なお知らせがあるので最後までしっかり聞いていってね。
Now, I have some important announcements from here on,
so please listen carefully until the end.
まずは、お知らせ1つ目。アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ発売です！
First, the first announcement.
Aki Rosenthal 2026 Birthday Goods are now on sale!
今回はライブの世界観をギュッと楽しんでもらえるグッズを頑張って制作いたしました。
This time, we worked hard to create goods that allow
you to fully enjoy the world of the live performance.
なので、今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方はぜひ応援で購入していただくのもすごく嬉しいです。
So, if you thought today's live was great,
I'd be very happy if you could buy them to show your support.
それではまず1つ目のグッズ！
Now, for the first item!
Life is GAME ラバーマット！
Life is GAME Rubber Mat!
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました。素敵なイラストありがとうございます。
The illustration for this one was drawn by LAM-sensei.
Thank you for the wonderful illustration.
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています。
It's an illustration inspired by the world
of today's live performance.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけどかっこいいようなアキロゼになっています。
It features an AkiRoze that's incredibly sexy and alluring,
yet cool at the same time.
ラバーマットで思う存分楽しんでください。
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with this rubber mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにぴったり。
By the way, the size is perfect for card games.
この意味わかるよね？
You know what that means, right?
2つ目のグッズが、運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット！
The second item is the "5 Cards of Fate"
Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set!
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます。
AkiRoze will tell your fortune
and give you a push of encouragement.
1日の始まりや、何か運命を託したいみたいなそんな時に
At the start of your day, or when you want
to entrust something to fate...
使って楽しむ、そして5枚バーンって飾っておけるので、見ても楽しめるようになっております。
...you can use them to enjoy, and since you can display all five,
they're also great to look at.
占い方法は、この後紹介するアキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております。
The fortune-telling method is linked with the
AkiRoze ASMR voices I'll introduce later.
飾っても楽しい、使っても楽しい、そのような連動グッズになっているのでぜひゲットしてください。
It's a linked item that's fun to display and fun to use,
so please be sure to get it.
続いてのグッズは、アキロゼのトランプ！
The next item is AkiRoze Playing Cards!
作っちゃいました！
I went ahead and made them!
こちら、実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので、たくさん予備も買ったほうがいいんじゃないかなと思います。
These are actual playing cards you can use, so I think
it might be a good idea to buy plenty of spares.
ぜひトランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんでアピールもしてくださいね。
Please enjoy plenty of AkiRoze through these cards
and show them off too.
続いては、こちら。アキロゼのカードケース！
Next is this one. AkiRoze Card Case!
合皮はもちろんトランプなど小物入れても大丈夫です。
Of course, you can put playing cards or other small items
in this synthetic leather case.
ぜひお家や持ち歩きに使ってね。
Please use it at home or for carrying things around.
そして、ボイスの紹介です。
And now, an introduction to the voices.
今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売！
We're releasing special ASMR voices this time too!
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも？
Aki and Roze might tempt you
from the left and right sides respectively.
台本も頑張って書いたのでぜひぜひたっぷり楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I worked hard on the script, so I'd be very happy
if you could enjoy it to the fullest.
こちらボイスは『Life is GAME ～アキとロゼの盤上～』こちらをメインとし
The main voice is "Life is GAME ~On the Board with Aki and Roze~"...
ASMRショートボイスとして、先ほどの『運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルカード』と連動したショートボイスが入っております。
...and as ASMR short voices, we have ones linked to the
"5 Cards of Fate" Tarot-style Acrylic Cards.
ショートボイスのシャッフル・ランダム再生をして選ばれたボイスがあなたの運命の1枚になります。ぜひ色々楽しんでね。
By shuffling and playing the short voices randomly, the one
selected will be your card of fate. Please have fun with it.
これらのグッズすべてが詰まったフルセット購入にはなんと特典も付いております。
Purchases of the full set, which includes all these items,
even come with a bonus.
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使ったチケット風カードになっております。
It's a ticket-style card featuring
the key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？ 参加したい？ こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているのでぜひゲットしてください。
Will you join this game? Want to join?
This is also an item that enhances the live performance's atmosphere.
そして、数量限定あります。
And, there are limited quantities available.
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております。頑張って書きます。
This one includes a handwritten signature
and a foil-stamped replica message. I'll do my best.
そして、数量限定が終わり次第、箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入ったチケット風カードになります。
Once the limited quantity is gone, it will be a ticket-style
card with a foil-stamped replica signature and message.
ぜひフルセット購入特典ゲットしてね。
Please be sure to get the full set purchase bonus.
大事な発売時間は、この後 21時30分。21時30分にショップオープンです。
The important sale time is 9:30 PM.
The shop opens at 9:30 PM.
ぜひ登録など準備して備えておいてね。
Please prepare by registering and be ready.
続きまして、お知らせ2つ目。この後 21時45分からメンバー限定のアフターライブを行います！
Moving on to the second announcement. We'll be holding a
members-only after-live starting from 9:45 PM tonight!
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なのでぜひお楽しみに。
I plan to perform different songs from the main live,
so please look forward to it.
今日メンバーになった方もぜひぜひ見てね。
Even if you just became a member today, please do watch it.
ちなみに過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも見れちゃうと思うのでぜひその...
By the way, I think you can also watch members-only
after-lives from past performances, so please...
後でも見てみてね。
Check it out later too.
ちなみに今回のサムネイルイラストは、
By the way, this time's thumbnail illustration...
メンバー限定で壁紙としてプレゼント予定です。
will be given as a wallpaper exclusively for members.
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
そして、お知らせ3つ目！
And the third announcement!
本日の生誕祭ライブの後も...
After today's birthday live...
お楽しみはまだまだ続きます。
the fun continues on.
なんと、Holoearthにて特別企画、
Amazingly, a special project on Holoearth...
アキ・ローゼンタール生誕祭アンコール in Holoearthを開催します！
Aki Rosenthal Birthday Encore in Holoearth will be held!
今回初披露した新曲『モノポリー』をHoloearthで歌っちゃいます！
I'll be singing the new song 'Monopoly', performed for the first time today, on Holoearth!
いろんな角度からアキロゼのパフォーマンスや
Please take a good look at AkiRose's performance and...
演出をじっくりと見てみてくださいね。
production from various angles.
さらに、HoloearthだけのMCパートも
Furthermore, there's a lot of MC parts...
たっぷりあるので、ぜひぜひ会いに来てください！
only for Holoearth, so please come see me!
開催日は3月13日、3月13日です。
The event date is March 13th, March 13th.
詳細はHoloearth公式Xをチェックしてね。
Check the official Holoearth X for details.
そして、最後のお知らせが... 新曲『モノポリー』！
And the final announcement is... the new song, 'Monopoly'!
本日日付が変わる頃にリリースされますので、
It will be released around midnight tonight,
各音楽配信サービスからぜひ購入してね。
so please buy it from music distribution services.
たくさん聴いてね！
Listen to it a lot!
振り付けも歌もとってもキャッチーなので、
Both the choreography and the song are very catchy,
覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる、愛されるような楽曲になってくれたら嬉しいなって思っています。
so I hope it becomes a song everyone can enjoy and love.
また後日ライブ配信で新曲『モノポリー』だったり、
Also, in a later stream, I want to talk about 'Monopoly' or...
今回のライブに触れた後日談など語ったり、一緒に見たりなどしたいなと思ってるので、
share stories from today's live and watch it together,
ぜひチャンネル登録、高評価ポチ、通知もオン！
so please subscribe, hit the like button, and turn on notifications!
忘れてた人は今ポチッとしてね！
If you forgot, hit them now!
絶対絶対また会いに来てね！
Definitely, definitely come to see me again!
それでは。
And now...
運命は時に残酷。
Fate is sometimes cruel.
あなたが選びたくて選んだものではないかもしれない。
It might not be what you wanted to choose.
だけど、いつでもあなたの人生は、あなたのもの。
But your life is always yours.
人生は一度きり。
Life is only once.
やり直しのきかないこのゲーム。
This game that cannot be redone.
あなたは、どう楽しむ？
How will you enjoy it?
【主催者】アキ・ローゼンタール
[Organizer] Aki Rosenthal
【出演者】赤見かるび, 天鬼ぷるる, ズズ, 律可, 癒月ちょこ, 森カリオペ, 鷹嶺ルイ, IRyS, 水宮枢, AZKi, 大神ミオ
[Performers] Karubi Akami, Pururu Amaki, Zuzu, Rikka, Choco Yuzuki, Mori Calliope, Lui Takane, IRyS, Kaname Mizumiya, AZKi, Mio Ookami
【振付制作】ミユキニシジマ
[Choreography] Miyuki Nishijima
【サムネイルイラスト】澄夜 咲星
[Thumbnail Illustration] Sumiya Sakise
【ロゴ制作】柊椋
[Logo Production] Hiiragi Muku
【Special Thanks】ロゼ隊, ALL STAFF and You
[Special Thanks] Rose-tai, ALL STAFF and You
Life is GAME
Member Only After Live
END